The losing teams of the main match,
Team KAIST and Team SNU in STEM,
will now begin today's Deathmatch.
It's time we got a bit of action.
Let's focus on keeping our cool, guys.
Team KAIST got dragged
into the Deathmatch because of us,
despite coming in second,
so I felt like we owed them
for falling behind.
But in a Deathmatch,
there's no room for such sentimentality.
All right.
I'd be lying
if I said I don't blame them.
But I'd rather take this as a chance
to prove that KAIST is the best in STEM.
Today's Deathmatch is...
Lucky 21.
Lucky 21?
- Will it involve numbers?
- Probably.
- Sounds like blackjack, no?
- Yeah.
The goal in that game
is to get 21 points as well.
In Lucky 21,
you will be presented with a 7-by-7 board.
You will be given time
to memorize the 49 numbered tiles
and then take turns to obtain them.
Your task is to make a set of 3 tiles
that add up to 21 to earn points.
It's a memorization game.
Jong-yun has an edge in memorization.
ACED THE MEMORIZATION QUIZ IN THE PRE-TEST
I felt certain I would win.
The numbered tiles include
special tiles and basic tiles.
The special tiles include
the number 7 tiles
and the ones marked with a clover.
There are 4 tiles of the number 7
and 7 tiles marked with a clover.
The remaining 38 tiles are the basic ones.
They named it "lucky"
because of the clover.
During the match,
only the backside of the tiles
will be displayed.
At the outset, one game piece
will be placed in the center of the board.
You can move the piece
WITHIN THE 30-SECOND LIMIT
up to 3 cells at your turn.
But the first player can move it
only one cell on their initial turn.
Additionally, you cannot reverse
your opponent's previous move,
or move the piece diagonally.
Once the piece reaches your destination,
you must perform
one of the following four actions.
Your first option is "checking."
If you ask for checking,
the tile's number will be shown
to you and your opponent.
Then it will be returned to its place
with the backside showing.
They should avoid that option, right?
You see it together,
so that should be your final resort.
If you're good enough,
you won't ask for that option.
Yes, if you're good enough.
Your second option is "obtaining."
You can obtain the tile
once the piece reaches its stop.
You can only keep
up to four tiles at a time.
What happens if you get more?
Your third option is "discarding."
Oh, so that's an option.
You can take the piece
to a cell without a tile
and discard one of the tiles
in your possession.
- That changes the layout.
- Right.
That's wild.
If the other guy takes a tile from here
and discards it over there,
- that changes the whole setup.
- This reminds me of Match and Mix.
GAME FROM SEASON 1
The board keeps changing
from the one in your memory.
Your fourth option is "taking a pass."
You can choose not to do anything
and complete your turn.
Proceed with the game
until the sum of 3 tiles
in your possession reaches 21.
Then, you can log the set.
You win one point
if your set consists of the basic tiles.
If your set is a trio of Tile 7s
or a trio of clover tiles,
you win two points.
If your set contains
both basic and special tiles,
you win one point.
Keep winning points
by logging suitable sets.
The first to secure four points
wins the round.
Your priority should be Tile 7s.
You can double the point
with a set of special tiles.
It might not be a bad idea
to memorize just the special tiles.
That's one possible strategy.
Suppose you take the tiles
and log your sets non-stop.
Two-pointers will get you a quicker win.
If a player obtains two Tile 7s,
the other has to claim the remaining ones.
Otherwise, they lose two points.
You can make
one special request per round,
either the "Move 5 Cells" card
or the "Discard 1 Tile" card.
The choice is up to you.
If you use the Move 5 Cells card,
you can move the piece up to 5 cells.
If you use the Discard 1 Tile card,
you can place the tile
on any empty cell of your choice
without consuming your turn.
That may be more helpful.
You can discard a tile
when the sum isn't 21.
There will be three rounds in total.
Rounds 1 and 2 require different players,
but anyone can participate in Round 3.
- Let's go get them.
- All right.
Your time has come.
Good luck.
As Team KAIST apprehended the culprit
in Signal Investigation 3 in less time,
they will decide which team goes first.
Both teams,
please start discussing your strategies.
You'll be given 20 minutes.
Hit me up with ideas.
Should we go first or second?
If we go first,
we'll literally get one more tile.
Can we make them go first
and take a Tile 7 on our turn?
- You want us to go second?
- Yes.
If you think about it,
the best tile to secure first is a Tile 7.
- For sure.
- With three Tile 7s,
we can get ahead with two points
even if they win a point first.
So one option is to lock in,
memorize their locations, and secure them.
Suppose we go second.
Can we guarantee a Tile 7
with the Move 5 Cells card?
You got a point.
- That's right up my alley.
- Great.
Being on the offensive.
It's very aggressive.
I love that about it.
Let me sum it up for you, Jong-yun.
Crush their spirits
with your great memory.
There's no need to overthink it.
All right.
You've got a brilliant memory, anyway.
Memorizing the board
was central to the game.
There was a movable game piece,
but whoever memorized the 49-tile board
was set to win the match.
By design, Jong-yun would excel
because of his amazing memory.
It seemed like the perfect chance
for Jong-yun to shine.
I've trained myself
with the mind palace technique.
By using this method, I was able
to memorize the 40 double-digit numbers
in under five minutes on the pre-test.
I think I'm the best at memorization
out of the remaining eight contestants.
My strategy is to memorize the whole board
so I don't need to check any tiles.
I'll use all of my 30 seconds
to make my opponent's memory fade.
That's the best game plan
if that doesn't affect your memory.
What technique do you use again?
A photographic memory
or creating a sequence?
Basically, I turn the information
into a sequence.
How? By making up a story?
Yes.
I have five compartments in my mind.
If I want to know the number here,
I would retrieve it from my memory
by visiting the mental space it is in.
To speed up the process,
I would link the physical location
with my mental compartment
housing that information.
I'll need to use all 30 seconds anyway,
and during that time,
my opponent would forget bits and pieces.
Any tips on memorizing efficiently?
- That's the key.
- It sure is.
Memorization...
Let's say we manage to get a Tile 7
by taking advantage of going second.
Find pairs whose sum reaches 14 or 21
during the memorization time
and hold on to their coordinates,
not the individual numbers.
So our top priority
is the locations of Tile 7s,
followed by the locations of pairs
that add up to 14?
Just their locations
without the exact numbers.
We can use these pairs
unless they take one of the tiles.
Initially, I thought memorization
would be the most important aspect.
But as you know, there is a limit
to how much you can remember.
So I needed a foolproof plan to win,
even if my memory wasn't the best.
Memorizing by pairs seems effective.
When you have a pair's location
but end up having to check
because you feel unsure,
you learn about 2 tiles
while your opponent only learns of 1.
Oh, that's true.
If memorization isn't their forte,
their focus will be on the special tiles.
We should obtain them first
to disrupt their game plan
and hopefully score two points on our end.
Here's an idea.
Don't make it your goal
- to get two-point sets.
- That's the key.
But you should still
try to get special tiles.
You can always complete your set
with a suitable basic tile.
We can then prevent Team KAIST
from scoring two points
- and win 4 times with 1 pointers.
- With steady progress.
If the round drags on,
they'll have to check the tiles.
I can go over what I've memorized
as they spend their 30 seconds.
- I must prolong the game to win.
- Yeah.
Any volunteers?
My gut tells me this is your thing.
- I guess I can do it.
- Good.
Anyone else?
I don't think
memorization will be so difficult.
You mean when you memorize by pairs,
as we discussed?
No, the whole board.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I can't say how long I'll remember,
but I think I can manage that
at the start.
- I'll win Round 1 for us.
- Yes, do that.
Want to take on Round 2, Ji-hoo?
Team SNU in STEM will send in
Mr. Chess Player and Mr. Hunter.
Well, probably.
I can see Mr. Hunter on their roster.
I mean, Dong-geon.
They did great in the pre-test.
They took most of the top four spots.
- In STEM Division.
- Yes, exactly.
Hey, hang on.
- That doesn't matter.
- Of course not.
You bet. I can take them.
I think we'll win.
I've got a good feeling about this.
- Wait, who's playing in Round 2?
- You guys can sort that out.
I'll take on Round 3
if Round 1 doesn't turn into a disaster.
- I can give it a go.
- Go for it if you'd like.
Wait, will you be using the same strategy?
- I'll decide after--
- He's going to memorize everything.
I'll memorize the tiles on the border.
They won't want the piece over there.
I thought it was very unlikely
they'd memorize the border tiles.
Since we could move up to three cells,
I could reach the border from any point.
I could keep up to four tiles.
Even if I had to pick up tiles
from the section I hadn't memorized,
I could find a suitable tile
from tapping into my memory
and complete a set that adds up to 21.
I thought this would give me
more freedom to maneuver the piece.
Hey, that's pretty good.
I'll memorize these parts only.
Can you get to the border from any point?
Of course. The nearest border cell
will always be within three cells.
That's true.
- What if you get crushed?
- Come on.
I'm going to blindside them.
A surprise tactic does sound promising.
Everyone else will focus on the center
because the piece will keep crossing it.
If I'm going second, I'll be okay
with the border and the special tiles.
Let's mull it over as we watch Round 1.
The time for strategy meeting is up.
You're going to be unbeatable.
Go out there with confidence.
- I can take them.
- Just be yourself.
You're not stressed, right?
You've got this. This is your forte.
I need to deliver here.
I know I've got to.
- SNU!
- For independence!
- Let's go!
DEATHMATCH
LUCKY 21
We will now begin
the Deathmatch, Lucky 21.
Players competing in Round 1
are Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min
and Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please come to the stage.
Let's have a good game.
As Team KAIST
held a higher rank in the main match,
their player will decide who goes first.
Please make your choice.
I'll go second.
Team KAIST chose to go second.
Here is your board for Lucky 21.
You'll be given four minutes to memorize.
It's best to get Clover Tile 11.
That will play a critical role.
You can pair it with 8-2, 6-4, or 9-1.
WITH CLOVER TILE 11,
YOU CAN MAKE 3 SETS THAT ADD UP TO 21
The time for memorization is over.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun
will go first.
You can only move one cell
in your initial turn.
Please move the piece.
AS PLANNED, HAN JONG-YUN TAKES HIS TIME
You have ten seconds left.
I'll obtain the tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
CLOVER 8
He claimed Clover Tile 8.
He can make a 2-pointer set with 9 and 4.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
I'll obtain the tile.
Smart move.
That Clover Tile 11 will be pivotal.
BOTH PLAYERS SECURED ONE CLOVER TILE EACH
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
You have ten seconds left.
I'll obtain the tile.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
I'll obtain the tile.
OBTAINED TILE 7, A SPECIAL TILE
FROM CLOVER TILES TO TILE 7S
He must've changed his target.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
You have ten seconds left.
I'll obtain the tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
CLOVER 8, 5, 9
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
I'll obtain the tile.
That's a Tile 7.
JEON JI-MIN:
7, 7, CLOVER 11
He knows Tile 7s' exact locations.
LOCATIONS OF THE REMAINING TILE 7S
The other Tile 7s are too far away.
He has to take the piece downward.
I doubt Jong-yun will let him do that.
You have ten seconds left.
I'll obtain the tile.
What was that?
He took that tile?
That has 14 on it.
THE SUM DOESN'T REACH 21
I got concerned because Jong-yun
seemed noticeably nervous.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
I'll take a pass.
- Where is another Tile 7?
- In the border.
It's on the lower right side.
JONG-YUN CAN SECURE A TILE 7 IN 1 TURN
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
HIS HAND IS FULL
He has to get the piece away from Tile 7s.
I decided that getting the piece away
from Tile 7s was more important.
I'll discard a tile.
It's 14.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
I'll use the Move 5 Cells card.
I'll obtain the tile.
TEAM KAIST LOGS A SET OF SPECIAL TILES
Dang, I can't believe
he built a set of Tile 7s.
That was amazing.
Unbelievable.
That means he memorized the whole board.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min won two points.
I wanted to keep the momentum going
and take the first round.
He's managing the game perfectly.
I guess they planned
to collect a trio of Tile 7s.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
It will be difficult to catch up
unless he gets a trio of clover tiles.
I'll obtain the tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
CLOVER 8, 5, 9, 5
Hang on.
THE SUM DOESN'T REACH 21
I guess something went wrong.
I made a basic calculation mistake
while rushing myself to win a point.
It seemed like Jong-yun fumbled
because my play got under his skin.
That boosted my confidence.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
I'll obtain the tile.
He has two clover tiles.
- Wasn't Clover Tile 4...
- It's just 3 cells away.
You're right.
THE PIECE IS CLOSE TO CLOVER TILE 4
The game is over
if Jong-yun can't recall that now.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
THE PIECE MOVES AWAY FROM CLOVER TILE 4
I'll discard a tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
CLOVER 8, 5, 9
I'll take a pass.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
You have ten seconds left.
You have five seconds left.
I'll take a pass.
That's a deathblow, no?
JEON JI-MIN CAN OBTAIN
CLOVER TILE 4 IN THE NEXT TURN
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
TEAM KAIST'S TURN
I'll obtain the tile.
- It's over.
- Yes, it is.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min
logged a set of tiles.
He won 2 points
as it consists of 3 special tiles.
TEAM KAIST: 4, TEAM SNU IN STEM: 0
Round 1 ends with Team KAIST's victory.
Wow, he's good.
Ji-min's really good.
He's brilliant.
That was simply perfect, sir.
The board is pretty easy to memorize.
I had it all memorized.
Doesn't it just mean
he's got an excellent memory?
I feel like we're unbeatable.
JI-MIN WILL COMPETE AGAIN IN ROUND 3
Don't worry. Making a comeback
from a mistake is always tricky.
I did poorly even after assuring my team
that memorization was my specialty.
I felt too ashamed to face them.
Ji-min is just that good.
How are we going to counter
their strategy?
- With the special tiles.
- We need the special tiles.
- Jong-yun made a mistake early on.
- Yes, it was a simple mistake.
I should've paid more attention
to the special tiles.
I'll have to memorize the numbers
on the special tiles as well.
We can't fall to Team KAIST.
Don't worry. I've got this.
We will now begin Round 2
of the Deathmatch, Lucky 21.
Both teams, please announce
which contestant will play in Round 2.
Here. I'm playing on my team's behalf.
I'm competing in this round.
I hope Team SNU in STEM wins this time.
I don't know why, but I'm getting nervous.
Isn't he the hunter from before?
You mean Dong-geon?
He was their hunter.
Yeah, he killed it.
As Team SNU in STEM lost Round 1,
their player will decide who goes first.
I'll go first.
You chose to go first.
It's better to go second.
I don't think so.
I did feel nervous going in,
but I was also excited
to take on the Deathmatch game.
I didn't feel so nervous
because the last Deathmatch hardened me.
I felt confident I could take him.
Here is your board for Lucky 21.
You'll be given four minutes to memorize.
It's a tougher arrangement.
This one's harder to memorize.
It will be hard to memorize it.
Dong-geon's strategy
will pay off big time.
I'll memorize the tiles on the border.
DONG-GEON'S STRATEGY
IS TO MEMORIZE THE BORDER TILES
I thought Team KAIST's strategy was
to get two-point sets with special tiles.
So I memorized their locations first
and moved on to the border section.
- Because of the clover tiles there?
- Yes.
- And all the Tile 7s.
- On top of those...
You just get a lot to work with.
The time for memorization is over.
Team SNU in STEM's Kim Dong-geon
will go first.
He'll go for Clover Tile 2, right?
I'll obtain the tile.
KIM DONG-GEON:
CLOVER 2
I hope he'll kick us off
with Clover Tile 13.
With Clover Tile 13,
Dong-geon's Clover Tile 2 is neutralized.
In this setup, Clover 2 Tile needs
2 specific tiles for a 2-point set.
The only possible 2-point set
consists of Clover Tiles 2, 6, and 13.
I'll obtain the tile.
KANG JI-HOO:
CLOVER 13
He went for the clover tile first.
He knows what Dong-geon is after.
DONG-GEON CAN'T MAKE A 2-POINT SET
WITH CLOVER TILE 2
I'll obtain the tile.
KIM DONG-GEON:
CLOVER 2, CLOVER 6
TEAM KAIST'S TURN
I really hope Ji-hoo forgets stuff.
Please let him forget.
- I can't watch this.
- What?
I can't bear to watch.
I'll obtain the tile.
BOTH PLAYERS COLLECTED SPECIAL TILES ONLY
Good job.
That's Tile 7.
They're trying to keep each other
from getting the special tiles.
TEAM SNU IN STEM'S TURN
I'll obtain the tile.
KIM DONG-GEON:
CLOVER 2, CLOVER 6, 8
I'll take a pass.
I'll use the Move 5 Cells card.
That should be used
only when you can get a tile
to complete your set.
I'll obtain the tile.
TEAM SNU IN STEM LOGS A SET OF BASIC TILES
Team SNU in STEM's Kim Dong-geon
won one point.
He wanted to secure a point first.
I'll obtain the tile.
KANG JI-HOO:
CLOVER 13, 7, 8
I'll obtain the tile.
KIM DONG-GEON:
CLOVER 2, CLOVER 1
I'll obtain the tile.
KANG JI-HOO:
CLOVER 13, 7, 8, CLOVER 5
THEY'RE TRYING TO NEUTRALIZE
THE OTHER'S SPECIAL TILES
Round 2 is more intense than Round 1.
I'll obtain the tile.
I'll take a pass.
Ji-hoo is holding onto so many tiles...
I know. Why won't he discard any of them?
I'll take a pass.
Team KAIST's Kang Ji-hoo.
Please move the piece.
WHOEVER SECURES TILE 3 FIRST
CAN LOG A SET OF TILES
I'll take a pass.
- What?
- I think Dong-geon is leading him on
- I think so, too.
- to get to the tile he wants.
Take it to that empty cell.
You have to discard a tile, Mr. KAIST.
I'll take a pass.
I could tell most of the tiles
Ji-hoo had memorized were gone.
I'll obtain the tile.
He did it.
He must've remembered that Tile 3 there.
Team SNU in STEM's Kim Dong-geon
logged a set of tiles.
TEAM KAIST: 0, TEAM SNU IN STEM: 2
Two points in total.
He's making steady progress.
Slow and steady like the mining operation.
He keeps including a special tile.
That way, he's likely to win.
Yes, Dong-geon is getting the upper hand.
I could remember everything,
so I knew I would win
the longer the game went on.
I'll discard a tile.
So I felt good about my chances.
I'll obtain the tile.
Team SNU in STEM's Kim Dong-geon
logged a set of tiles.
ONE MORE POINT,
AND TEAM SNU IN STEM WINS THIS ROUND
There we have it.
Please...
I'll obtain the tile.
My only way out
was to claim the Tile 7 trio.
I knew I would win in the end.
KIM DONG-GEON:
10, 2, 8
Move one cell up.
Take it just one cell up.
DONG-GEON CAN LOG A SET OF TILES
IF HE OBTAINS TILE 9 NEXT
Team SNU in STEM's Kim Dong-geon.
Please move the piece.
I'll obtain the tile.
He did it!
Kudos to his memory.
Kudos indeed.
He definitely has a sharp memory.
He kept the board memorized
throughout the game.
Yes, he retained it throughout.
Team SNU in STEM's Kim Dong-geon
won a point.
Round 2 ends
with Team SNU in STEM's victory.
TEAM KAIST: 0, TEAM SNU IN STEM: 4
What a shame.
That concludes Round 2 of Lucky 21.
How many cells did you memorize?
- The whole board, of course.
- Really?
No, I was just kidding.
I was relieved
that my strategy
to focus on the border was effective.
I think the winners will play in Round 3.
- That's for sure.
- Right?
- That should be interesting.
- I know.
I'd say Ji-min and Dong-geon
will compete next.
If they get a face-off,
Ji-min will surely win.
- Great job.
- Thank you.
That's how it's done.
You did us a solid.
It's such a shame.
Don't worry about it.
You gave it a nice sense of suspense.
You spiced things up for the show.
I'll get us the win in Round 3.
We will now begin Round 3
of the Deathmatch, Lucky 21.
Both teams, please announce
which contestant will play in Round 3.
Will it be Dong-geon?
Of course.
If they don't throw us a curve, sure.
Team SNU in STEM.
I'll be playing.
HAN JONG-YUN WILL COMPETE
Didn't Jong-yun compete in Round 1?
They're going with Jong-yun.
AGAINST ALL EXPECTATION,
HAN JONG-YUN GOES FOR ROUND 3
AFTER ROUND 2
What do we do about Round 3?
Let Jong-yun compete.
My mind's pretty exhausted.
I knew how good Jong-yun was
at memorization,
so I was convinced
that he'd do far better than I
if he memorized
where the special tiles were.
- You actually want to compete, right?
- Yes.
I hope you're not offering
because you want to oblige.
- Your opinion matters most.
- You've got this.
Think about it.
I know I'm being greedy here.
- If you're up for it, you should do it.
- Agreed.
To be honest...
I don't think I did my part
during our game yesterday,
so I want to tackle the final game myself.
If you want that, you can go for it.
You totally should.
- That game's built for you.
- No pressure, though. You've got this.
- For sure.
- Thank you, guys.
I realized I should pull myself together
instead of floundering.
Put your memory to good use,
and you're bound to win.
Good luck. I know you've got this.
I've got this.
Team KAIST.
I'll play on my team's behalf.
TEAM KAIST'S PLAYER, JEON JI-MIN
It's basically a rematch.
- It's the same lineup from Round 1.
- You're right.
Jong-yun must've felt
he could win this time.
I guess he revised his strategy.
He's probably determined
to get his payback.
- His strategy must've been faulty.
- I agree.
He must have an impeccable one now.
I think Team SNU will make a comeback.
I'll come back victorious.
- Good luck.
- You've got this.
- Go get them.
- Best of luck.
Jong-yun got overwhelmed
by my prowess in Round 1.
So I had the feeling
I might get another good game.
Good luck. You can beat him.
Dong-geon.
- Thanks for the opportunity.
- Good attitude.
- Good luck.
- Let's roll.
- I'll get us the win.
- I know you can do it.
Dong-geon gave me the chance
to make up for my failure,
so I felt more determined
to win the round.
Players competing in Round 3 are
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun
and Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
This is the real drama.
It's what epics are made of.
As Team KAIST lost Round 2,
their player will decide who goes first.
- He'll probably go second.
- Yeah.
- Same as Round 1, right?
- He won then.
I'll go second.
Here's your board for Lucky 21.
You'll be given four minutes to memorize.
- Thank goodness.
- Why did you say that?
Jong-yun's going first,
so he can get Clover Tile 8.
- Clover tiles are nearby. See?
- Hey, you're right.
- It's better to go first.
- Definitely.
I don't see multiple sets
except the ones using Clover Tile 8.
Jong-yun will likely take it at the start.
It will be difficult to make sets
with the clover tiles.
I'm worried about the clover tiles.
I've only found two possible sets so far.
3, 8, 10 AND 4, 8, 9
ARE THE ONLY POSSIBLE CLOVER SETS
We can count on Jong-yun's memory...
- So it's for the better.
- I'm sure he'll deliver results.
The time for memorization is over.
I think this round will be fun.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun
will go first.
You can move only one cell at this time.
Please move the piece.
- He'll take Clover Tile 8, won't he?
- You bet he will.
I'll obtain the tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
CLOVER 8
Jong-yun's ringing voice implied
that he was fully back in the game.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
I'll obtain the tile.
JEON JI-MIN:
CLOVER 9
Was that a defensive move?
JONG-YUN CAN'T MAKE
THE CLOVER SET OF 4, 8, AND 9
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
Looks like Jong-yun is reviewing things.
- Yes.
- He's retrieving the numbers.
JONG-YUN IS WORKING IN HIS "MIND PALACE"
He's looking for his playmates.
Yeah, he's rummaging around
to find the thief and the puppets.
I'll obtain the tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
CLOVER 8, 7
I'll obtain the tile.
JEON JI-MIN:
CLOVER 4, CLOVER 9
- Both are on defense.
- Exactly.
It's getting fierce.
I think I saw a Tile 7
on the bottom right side.
I'll obtain the tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
CLOVER 8, 7, 7
He has two Tile 7s, right?
Yes, I think so.
I thought the game was progressing
as I had planned.
You have ten seconds left.
I'll take a pass.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
Time is on our side.
I'm sure Jong-yun remembers everything.
- Jong-yun needs one more Tile 7.
- They're in the upper section.
One in the middle and one at the top.
One wrong move, and Jong-yun will use
the Move 5 Cells card to get one.
Ji-min shouldn't move it up.
It looks like Ji-min is trying
to figure out a way to avoid that.
You have five seconds left.
I'll obtain the tile.
JEON JI-MIN:
CLOVER 10, CLOVER 4, CLOVER 9
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
I'll use the Move 5 Cells card.
There we go. He's moving it up.
- All right. He needs that Tile 7.
- Good call.
I'll use the Move 5 Cells card.
I'll obtain the tile.
I'll log my tile set.
A SET OF SPECIAL TILES
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun
logged a set of tiles.
He won 2 points
as it consists of 3 special tiles.
Your attitude can either make
or break the game.
That's why I tried to show
as much confidence as possible.
He won 2 points
as it consists of 3 special tiles.
- So he had a trio of Tile 7s.
- Yeah, he did.
Shoot, I get that now.
Ji-min can't get a two-pointer now.
- Three Tile 7s are out...
- Don't forget Clover Tile 8.
I'm getting an incredible dopamine rush.
Ji-min can't get any 2-point set
with Clover Tiles 10, 4, or 9.
- Ji-min's special tiles became useless.
- Exactly.
That was a mistake.
You have ten seconds left.
I'll take a pass.
I'll obtain the tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
CLOVER 8, 1
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
I'll use the Move 5 Cells card.
I'll obtain the tile.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min
logged a set of tiles.
He won a point.
He's going for 1-pointers.
Now, it all comes down
to how much they remember.
This will be a tough one.
I'll obtain the tile.
LOGS A SET OF TILES
He's become a different person.
He must've memorized
the whole board this time.
- He's getting his revenge for Round 1.
- Looks that way.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun
won a point.
TEAM KAIST: 1, TEAM SNU IN STEM: 3
He's progressing fast.
He won three points in no time.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
Thirteen... Twelve...
Time is definitely on our side.
It looks like
Jong-yun remembers everything.
I'll obtain the tile.
JEON JI-MIN:
2, CLOVER 9
I'll obtain the tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
I'll take a pass.
I'll obtain the tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
4, 9
IF HE SECURES TILE 8, HE WINS THE ROUND
Does he know where Tile 8s are?
- Where are they?
- Here.
And here, too.
- I think he'd know.
- Do you see it?
2 TILE 8S REMAIN ON THE BOARD
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
I'll obtain the tile.
JEON JI-MIN:
11, 2, CLOVER 9
Jong-yun can now get Tile 8.
- I see. He can get it.
- He sure can.
It's over if he recalls where Tile 8 is.
He has to go right, down, down.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
IF HE COLLECTS TILE 8,
THE ROUND ENDS IN A 4-1 VICTORY
- Let's go, man.
- Yeah, you've got this.
- Right, down, down.
- Exactly.
You have ten seconds left.
I'll...
Yes, I'll obtain it.
JONG-YUN PICKS UP TILE 5 INSTEAD OF TILE 8
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
JI-MIN TOOK THE PIECE TO TILE 8
I'll obtain the tile.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min
logged a set of tiles.
He won a point.
TEAM KAIST: 2, TEAM SNU IN STEM: 3
- Ji-min knew about it.
- Looks like it.
- That was a risky move.
- I know.
This is pretty sick.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
You have ten seconds left.
I'll take a pass.
TEAM KAIST'S TURN
Please make your choice.
I'll obtain the tile.
- It's over.
- Yeah!
Jong-yun should know about that Tile 8.
ANOTHER OPPORTUNITY TO OBTAIN TILE 8
I'll obtain the tile.
JONG-YUN FAILED TO SECURE TILE 8
He's forgotten about that.
Dang it.
Please make your choice.
I'll obtain the tile.
JEON JI-MIN:
9, 5, CLOVER 9
Ji-min wastes no time at all.
It's pretty intense.
Jong-yun has to discard a tile now.
WITH 4 TILES IN HIS POSSESSION,
JONG-YUN HAS TO DISCARD ONE
It seemed he didn't memorize everything.
I'll discard a tile.
I realized he was in a fog.
I set my mind on keeping this momentum.
Please make your choice.
I'll obtain the tile.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min
logged a set of tiles.
He won a point.
JI-MIN GAVE CHASE TO TIE THE GAME
It's neck-and-neck.
What a close game.
- It's 3-to-3.
- Anyone can win.
Come on now.
He's got an incredible memory.
- If he wins...
- I'm amazed.
Ji-min has managed to gain on Jong-yun.
When it's tied 3-3,
the one who doesn't mess up would win.
I felt unsettled
when Ji-min caught up with me,
but I still thought
I could win as long as I stayed focused.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
Please make your choice.
I'll take a pass.
I'll obtain the tile.
Please make your choice.
My heart.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
Please make your choice.
I'll take a pass.
I'll discard a tile.
I'll obtain the tile.
- I'll take a pass.
What a tight race.
I'm a wreck now. I can't stand this.
They're so set
on not revealing their goal.
They really should check the tiles,
but they're avoiding it
because it's so neck-and-neck.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
Please make your choice.
I'll obtain the tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
9, 16, CLOVER 6
After wracking my brain
to find a set whose sum reached 21
out of the tiles I memorized,
I finally found a suitable pair.
All I had to do was obtain them.
- Please make your choice.
- I'll take a pass.
I'll discard a tile.
- What's on that tile?
- It's 16.
HAN JONG-YUN:
9, CLOVER 6
WITH TILE 6, THE SUM WILL REACH 21
Are there more Tile 6s
other than the one above Tile 11?
There's one more in the upper left corner.
You're right.
It looks like Jong-yun can wrap it up now.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
You have ten seconds left.
I'll obtain the tile.
JEON JI-MIN:
9, 1, 4, 5,
I managed to get to the 3-3 tie
and claimed Tile 4 as I planned.
All I needed to win then was Tile 16.
JONG-YUN DISCARDED TILE 16
I thought, "That will get me the victory.
I'm on the brink of winning."
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
I'll obtain the tile.
HAN JONG-YUN:
9, 4, CLOVER 6
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please move the piece.
Please make your choice.
I'll discard my Tile 5.
Come on now. Surely not...
BOTH TEAMS NEED JUST ONE MORE TILE TO WIN
JONG-YUN'S TARGET: TILE 6
JI-MIN'S TARGET: TILE 16
Please make your choice.
I'll discard my Tile 4.
Jong-yun can reach that Tile 6
no matter what.
Ji-min can't reverse Jong-yun's last move,
so he won't have any problem.
As the piece cannot be returned
to its original place
from the previous turn,
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min can only take it
within the highlighted area.
Regardless of where he leaves it,
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun
can obtain Tile 6 on his next turn.
Please make your choice.
I'll take a pass.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun.
Please move the piece.
Please make your choice.
I'll obtain the tile.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun
logged a set of tiles.
He won a point.
I'm floored.
I was glad that I managed to repay
my teammates' trust with a victory.
I also felt relieved.
I was literally one tile away
from winning,
so I was racing to get it.
It was deeply upsetting
to have it slip through my fingers.
Team SNU in STEM's Han Jong-yun
won four points in total.
That concludes Round 3 of Lucky 21.
Round 3 ends
with Team SNU in STEM's victory.
- Thanks for the good game.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
- Thanks, man.
All I needed was one more turn.
- What a shame.
- It's so disappointing.
- Thank you for your trust.
- I loved your game.
You were amazing.
That concludes the Deathmatch, Lucky 21.
The third team to be eliminated
from Elite League Season 3 is
Team KAIST.
Will the light go out?
Oh, no. Don't turn off
the lovely sky blue light.
All teams surrounding us went home.
So lonely.
- I haven't had a face-off against Ji-hu.
- Oh, right.
Team KAIST, please exit the grounds.
- Should we get going?
- Yeah.
- Are we seriously leaving?
- Bummer.
It's such a shame.
Let's do our best.
Our clips will be on the web
for at least a decade.
This should be fun.
I basically waited two years
to be on the show, since I applied twice.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min
has been chosen as the Ace player.
I was so elated to be selected.
I had such a great time
playing the amazing games.
The two-year wait was so worth it.
...was correct.
My only regret is
that our joyful journey has to end.
What a bummer.
Thanks to my teammates, I made it so far
and got to play a bunch of fun games.
Now, we have to leave...
I still can't believe it.
I gave it my all until the end,
so I don't have any regrets left.
I'd like to thank the creators
for the opportunity.
Jae-han is a wiz with this stuff.
He's like a machine.
I probably wasn't the strongest contender,
but I loved tackling various tasks
with the help of my team.
I had so much fun competing here
with my teammates by my side.
I think I'll remember
my days here forever.
To be honest,
being on the show felt like a dream.
Along the way...
This is probably the day I solved
the most calculation questions in my life.
I do have my regrets,
but I did my very best.
My teammates also gave their all,
so I want to thank them for it.
I'm sorry.
- Don't be.
- My bad.
Don't say that.
You're here because you are good.
Excuse me.
We're splitting the prize, remember?
We'll have the 1-on-1 interviews now.
AFTER LUCKY 21
If you wait at the main hall...
ALL CONTESTANTS GATHER AT THE MAIN HALL
TEAM KAIST
THIRD TEAM TO BE ELIMINATED
They turned the lights off.
LIGHTS ARE OFF
OUTSIDE THE ELIMINATED TEAMS' BASE CAMPS
WAILING
Hey, the lights are off.
- They turned off the light.
- I know.
TEAM POSTECH
FIRST TEAM TO BE ELIMINATED
I hear you came in first.
TEAM YONSEI
SECOND TEAM TO BE ELIMINATED
So you killed it?
- It's been a while.
- Right.
- So you aced the main match?
- Yes, we did.
Tae-hun did the heavy lifting.
Be the champions, okay?
It's 2-against-1 now. You've got to win.
You bet we will.
We can't let Team SNU
win three seasons in a row.
Exactly.
You guys are my favorite.
- You're my favorite, okay?
- The feeling's mutual.
We had good chemistry, didn't we?
I'm sorry.
If we hadn't bungled the main match...
We should've done a better job
with the investigation.
How was the shoot yesterday?
Aren't you guys drained?
I went straight to bed after Day 1.
And I woke up at 3 p.m. the day after.
- I was that tired.
- Sounds lovely.
I'm so jealous.
You think it was lovely?
Are you making fun of us?
We are just messing with you.
What did you do at the hotel?
Us?
We wallowed in grief.
We grieved.
To be honest, I fell asleep right away,
but these folks had a sleepless night.
I finally fell asleep at 5 a.m.
A-in's crying face kept coming back to me.
Of course, you were heartbroken.
- It was upsetting.
- We were heartsick.
So, Ji-hu.
- You went to Hansung Science High?
- Yes.
- You graduated early, too?
KANG JI-HU, 17 YEARS OLD
How are you so bright when you're only 17?
His brain is young and supple.
- Back when I was 18...
- We were beasts.
We shook the whole universe.
- We will now begin a redemption round.
- What?
- Wait...
- Seriously?
What on earth?
Is this for real?
It makes no sense.
Seriously, what's going on?
- It's real.
- Are you serious?
What was our elimination interview for?
What on earth?
Maybe the game is on today.
- It's on right away.
- Right away?
The whole interview was a smoke screen.
They used it as a pretext
for the redemption round.
- Hang on.
- Just a second.
- Let's put our friendship on hold.
- Yeah, right.
We'll see you later.
We have a good chance of making it back.
We've got to take it.
Seriously though, we need you to advance.
- That way, we get a 3-to-1 setup.
- "Medical versus STEM,
- med students flatten their opponents."
- We need that.
Let's give it our all
like it's our Deathmatch.
A true Deathmatch
where the survivors return from hell.
This is exactly what we needed.
We will now begin the redemption round.
Oh, the lights are back on.
They turned them back on.
- Wow, the lights are on.
- They are.
Team POSTECH.
Team Yonsei.
Team KAIST.
With the exception of these three teams,
please return to your base camps.
Good luck, Team Yonsei!
- You've got this!
- Go get them!
- Good luck!
- You've got this!
All right!
- Good luck.
- Go get them!
Let's go, STEM Division!
We'll do our best!
Ji-hoo.
Hey, Ji-hoo.
FROM JI-HU TO JI-HOO
Good luck.
You've got this.
All right. Go, me!
This isn't exactly good news for us.
- I agree.
- Same here.
Things will get tricky
with Team KAIST back in the mix.
We barely managed to defeat them.
They're way too good.
We jumped through hoops
to get them eliminated.
If Team Yonsei makes it back,
- it will get rough for us.
- I know.
- We had such a close game.
- Exactly.
We won by a very narrow margin.
Who knows what will happen in a rematch?
Honestly though,
I was happy to see Team Yonsei leave.
This means
that we get one of our rivals back.
Tell me about it.
That will add the pressure.
None of them is a pushover.
It's frightening.
A true return from hell.
A redemption round?
But then again, it did feel like
things were going too well.
I wonder which team will make it back.
I think Team KAIST has the upper hand
since they played until this morning.
They could be worn out, though.
Team Yonsei had a good night's rest.
Let's say Team KAIST manages to advance.
Just imagine their day.
They would've traveled back and forth
from hell to heaven.
I still can't believe what's happening.
Our elimination was a surprise,
but that was nothing compared to this.
Those guys look so well-rested.
We're at a disadvantage.
That's true.
But we must rise above and win
to complete our hero's journey.
We'll overcome this.
We simply couldn't get eliminated again.
I was determined to claw our way back.
Let's pull ourselves together
and do better this time.
Let's give it our all
and leave no regrets.
That was our last shot.
Another defeat meant we were truly done.
We'll win this time
and make our way back into the game.
Remember how it felt when we got axed.
- Let's do our best.
- I'm all for that.
Imagine how cool it'd be
if we rose like a phoenix
and became the champions.
Totally.
- That's a perfect narrative.
- You bet.
I wanted to win no matter what.
I was ready to seize my shot.
The redemption round is...
Relay Match.
It's called the Relay Match.
It will be a one-on-one game.
Everyone will have to pull their weight.
In Relay Match,
the host will choose 1 game
out of 3 options.
Then, they will select one contestant
as their opponent.
The winner will be determined
by the head-to-head results.
An individual competition is long overdue.
The survivors should be the fittest.
Given the setup, one person
may single-handedly rescue their team.
This will be so much fun.
All teams will be assigned six lives.
You can freely divide them
between your teammates,
but please remember to assign
at least one life to each member.
This sounds so exciting.
- Won't Ji-min get three lives?
- Maybe.
They'll need to approach it strategically.
As Team KAIST
managed to survive the longest,
one of their members
will be the initial host.
The host can choose
the game they would like to play
and the contestant
they would like to compete against.
The winner's team
will be awarded one point.
Additionally,
the winner will be the next host.
The loser will lose one life.
When you lose all your lives,
you will be barred
from participating in the game.
It's a true fight to the death.
We'll get an all-out war.
The games will test you
on reasoning, spatial awareness,
and memorization.
Relay Match has 18 questions in total,
with 6 questions per game.
Each team can use the Priority card
once throughout the entire game.
Please note that it can only be used
within 30 seconds
after the host's selection.
The contestant who uses the Priority card
can compete against the host
instead of the opponent of their choice.
Like a substitute.
Secure points following these rules.
The team with the most points
will be declared the winner.
The winning team
will get their second chance
to rejoin the surviving teams
of the competition.
You've got this, right?
We have to do well.
- Let's do this.
- We've got this.
Our Ace player.
We're going to win.
We will now reveal the three games
of the redemption round, Relay Match.
The first game
will test your reasoning skills.
It is Time Jump.
In Time Jump,
your task is to fill in each blank
with one of the given numbers.
The first to make
the correct sentence wins.
You may be asked about dates as well.
USE NUMBERS FROM 1 TO 3
"One hour after 2 o'clock is 3 o'clock."
"Two hours after 1 o'clock is 3 o'clock."
There are multiple answers.
The second game
will test your spatial awareness.
It is Pixel Art.
"Pixel"? That may be like Pixel Number.
I don't get the "art" part.
In Pixel Art, you will be presented
with nine pixel cards in total.
Three of them will match the target
when layered together.
Your task is to find them first.
They have to be overlapped?
Oh, that sounds like fun!
When you combine the pixel cards,
you can rotate the cards
to get the target image.
Dang, I'm taking back what I just said.
- Shoot, did I just hear right?
- Oh, man.
That's tricky.
But the pixel cards may not be flipped
horizontally or vertically.
The three primary colors in Pixel Art
can be mixed to create secondary colors.
A red cell layered over a blue cell
will result in a violet cell.
A red cell layered over a yellow cell
will result in an orange cell.
A blue cell layered over a yellow cell
will result in a green cell.
When all three colors
are layered together,
you will get a black cell.
To get a secondary color,
the different colors
must be mixed at a 1-to-1 ratio.
But cells of the same color
can be layered without restrictions.
They've got to mix the colors?
That explains the art part.
The black cells
will be the ones to watch out for.
The black cells seem important, right?
Let's use the secondary colors
as our guide.
The third game
will test your memorization skills.
I hope we get a decent memorization game.
It is Photo Memory.
In Photo Memory,
you will be shown a set of 10 photos
for 10 seconds each to memorize.
You will then solve
nine questions in a row.
The player with more points wins the game.
- What on earth? That sounds outrageous.
- That's just insane.
It's not a simple memorization game.
This will actually require
a photographic memory.
That sounds like a blast, though.
- I can crush this.
- Really?
I can take down anyone
when it comes to pure brainpower shit.
Watch your language.
Sounds like only Pixel Art
requires strategies.
As for the rest, we can rely on our minds.
Here's the real problem.
What if Team KAIST won't choose us?
We'll use the Priority card
and claim the host position.
I see. Good idea.
I guess that's what the card is for.
All teams,
please start discussing your strategies.
You'll be given 20 minutes.
All the 1-on-1 games
were saved for this match.
It looks like so much fun.
This is pretty similar
to Mystery Poker from yesterday.
The more prepared you are,
- the less confused you get.
- Agreed.
Can I tell you
about the strategy for Pixel Art first?
Go ahead.
We can rotate the pixel cards, right?
Here's what I think.
Whichever way you rotate it,
the center cell will remain in the spot.
Why don't we use that as a guide
to sort out the cards?
I like the idea.
Look at this example.
Since the center cell is white,
we can exclude the cards
with a colored cell in the center.
EXCLUDE PIXEL CARDS WITH A COLORED CENTER
If the center cell is black,
we will need a combination
of red, yellow, and blue.
RED, BLUE, AND YELLOW ARE NEEDED
TO GET THE COLOR BLACK
That will help us narrow down cases.
Let's try this approach.
We can focus on the secondary colors,
violet, orange, and green.
Those narrow down cases to combinations
of white and two different colors.
You're absolutely right.
To get the three secondary colors
of violet, orange, and green in Pixel Art,
the relevant primary colors
must be mixed at a 1-to-1 ratio.
However,
you must use three pixel cards
to get the target image.
As this is the case,
you will need one white cell
to get the violet cell.
With secondary colors,
you need a set like white, red, and blue
or white, red, and yellow.
I think it's better to use them
to narrow things down.
- Good idea.
- That way,
we can easily eliminate a bunch of cards.
I think I can do a good job
with Pixel Art.
Rather than looking for three cards
that can give me the target,
I'll take the target image
and layer it over the cards.
Ji-min is suggesting a strategy
of placing the target on the cards.
This way,
you can eliminate
the unnecessary cards quickly.
I can weed out irrelevant cards
after comparing them to the target.
When three cards remain, I have my answer.
Layering the target over other cards
sounds pretty good.
Are there any hacks to Time Jump?
That's the game I'm worried about.
Why don't we use MOD 30?
With that...
Can you give me an example?
It sounds fuzzy to me.
Let's find out the date
81 days past August 17th.
Add 81 to 17. We get August 98th.
- Okay, next?
- Divide 98 by 30.
- Divide it by 30?
- Then, we get a quotient and a remainder.
Use the quotient to update the month.
Then, check how many months with 31 days
come between August and that month.
- Dock it out?
- Exactly.
August and October
both have 31 days, right?
Now, subtract 2 from 8.
Subtract 2 from 8?
Is the answer November 6th?
Yes.
The key is to correctly count
the months with 31 days.
Make sure to keep that in mind.
Let's move on to dates.
Ever heard of the Doomsday algorithm?
- Doomsday algorithm?
- I'll tell you all about it.
There's this chart
that lists one day in every month
that occurs on the same day of the week.
In January, it's the 10th.
February only has 28 days,
so it's going to be the 28th.
THE LISTED DATES ALL OCCUR
ON THE SAME DAY OF THE WEEK EVERY YEAR
Basically, all these days
occur on the same day of the week.
EXAMPLE
JANUARY 10TH IS A MONDAY
To find out which day September 7th is,
you can refer to the Doomsday algorithm
to learn that January 10th
and September 5th are both Mondays.
As September 7th
is 2 days past September 5th,
you can deduce
that September 7th is a Wednesday.
We can use this information
to tackle the date questions efficiently.
When it comes to people,
focus on noticeable traits
like wearing a headset.
Here's what I do
when I need to memorize anything.
Don't try to capture all the details.
Look at it from afar,
like you're gazing at a forest.
That way, we can get a general impression.
But short-term memory
is the key to memorization.
Hit the buzzer right away.
- Just go for it.
- That's a must.
If you miss something, you won't recall.
You need to at least
win a chance to answer.
Hands down.
Which game do you feel most confident in?
I'll be okay with any of them.
No, I feel good about all of them.
This guy has no weaknesses.
Do you want 2 lives or 3?
Right, we can give him three lives.
But three lives might keep people at bay.
Because they'll see Ji-min
as too big a threat?
Okay, then. I'll take two lives.
TEAM KAIST'S LIFE ALLOCATION
TEAM POSTECH'S LIFE ALLOCATION
TEAM YONSEI'S LIFE ALLOCATION
We'll have to win as many points as we can
when we get the initial host position.
Let's make the most of that perk
- and win a ton of points.
- We've got to.
Are you up for it?
I am, actually.
Just end it yourself.
- You can just...
- You want me to win 12 points?
- Yeah, go ahead.
- I'd love that.
Don't lose, Ji-min.
Both teams think we're lightweights.
They think we're the weaklings,
so they won't try to avoid us.
I think there's a chance
they won't even let us compete.
Well, I think that will be to our benefit.
Let them go head-to-head
and exhaust each other's lives--
Wait, the lives don't matter.
It's all about points.
You could even say
lives don't have much of an impact.
But not the points.
We must get a chance to compete
and earn points.
Even if we end up losing,
we've got to compete.
Let's say Team KAIST goes
after every member of Team POSTECH.
Team KAIST taking away
Team POSTECH's lives doesn't matter.
What matters is that they're taking
the points that could have been ours.
Here's my pitch.
If Team KAIST selects Team POSTECH
two times in a row,
we should use the Priority card.
We'll let them take two points,
but we'll get into the game from Round 3.
Remember the two guys besides Jun-u,
my opponent in the Deathmatch?
I think they have a bad memory.
Oh, I didn't say anything.
They seem like math and physics prodigies
who are terrible at memorization.
I think you need to be prepared.
- Okay.
- Got it?
There's a high chance
Team KAIST will come after you first.
Alternatively,
they might go after Team Yonsei.
They'll remember your performance
from the Deathmatch.
They've seen you get nervous,
so you'll be high on their target list.
- I want you to be mentally prepared.
- Okay, I will.
One more thing.
Let's say we get picked to compete.
Then, please remember
that this is a favorable setup for us.
So be confident
- and just think about winning, okay?
- Good point.
If there's any chance
you can control the situation,
leave Ji-hoo for me.
I want to take him down.
LEE JUN-U VOWS TO GET HIS REVENGE
FOR DOUBLE-SIDED BINGO
Let's not underestimate
Team KAIST and Team POSTECH.
Yeah, we need to focus.
There's a chance we might lose,
so let's keep our focus.
We don't want to regret it later.
- Think of this as a Deathmatch.
- It is a Deathmatch.
It's a three-way Deathmatch.
Let's make it back.
It's time to awaken the other me.
I have two souls inside of me.
Two hearts.
Yeah, two hearts.
BOTH HAVE 2 LIVES
The time for strategy meeting is up.
All teams, please gather
at the main hall for the match.
- KAIST!
- Let's go!
- POSTECH!
- Akaraka!
- Let's go, Yonsei!
We will now begin the redemption round,
Relay Match.
- This is going to be fun.
- It will be epic.
I hope Team KAIST doesn't return.
They're so scary.
I'd hate to face Ji-min in another game.
I hope this match will drain them.
Team KAIST, please announce
which contestant will play as the host.
I'll be the first host.
- All right, Ji-min.
- Ji-min.
He has a thunderous voice.
He has great energy.
Yeah, and his energy
can really throw you off.
He must have nerves of steel.
He's always confident.
It looks like Ji-min does
all the heavy lifting for Team KAIST.
He's their Ace player.
The host, Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min,
will now select the game.
6 QUESTIONS EACH
I wonder what he'll choose.
I'll go with Pixel Art.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min
selected Pixel Art.
Please choose your opponent.
Team KAIST's priority now
is to find the weakest team.
I think he'll go with Team POSTECH
because of their rivalry.
Sure, who can resist a rival match?
I'll play against
Team POSTECH's Hwang Seok-hun.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min
chose Team POSTECH's Hwang Seok-hun.
- Good luck out there. Don't get nervous.
- I won't.
- It's the first game, so no pressure.
- Good luck.
You've got this.
- Let's have a good game.
- Looking forward to it.
I really hope he'll do well.
I wanted to repay my friends' trust in me.
So I tried to empty my mind
and give the game my undivided attention.
I thought my mission was to stay
as the host as long as I could.
Basically, I had to win at all costs.
If Ji-min finishes Team POSTECH off,
- he can decide the match.
- Absolutely.
Remember how Team KAIST
shipped Team POSTECH off?
- In the Deathmatch?
- You're right.
Those two already had a face-off.
The first rival match
after the Deathmatch.
REUNION OF THE OLD RIVALS
Let us begin Pixel Art.
THEY MUST SELECT 3 PIXEL CARDS
- Dang, this is confusing.
- Totally.
I spotted a promising card,
but I can't find it now.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
I'll go with Pixel Cards 3, 7, and 8.
That is correct.
PIXEL CARDS 3 AND 7: 180-DEGREE ROTATION
PERFECT MATCH TO THE TARGET
How did he get it so quickly?
- That speed, though.
- How can he solve it so fast?
You've got to hand it to him.
Team POSTECH's Hwang Seok-hun.
You lost a life.
What a shame.
You still did a great job.
CURRENT STANDINGS
YONSEI: 0, KAIST: 1, POSTECH: 0
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please select the next game.
I'll go with Pixel Art.
Please choose your opponent.
It will get wild
if he chooses Seok-hun again.
That's so hardcore.
That's the right move
to secure your survival.
Call Seok-hun again.
I'll play against Team POSTECH's...
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu, please.
He's targeting people with two lives.
He's docking everyone's life.
Looks like he's planning
to wipe out Team POSTECH.
Here is your question.
TARGET
Pixel Card 1's a must, no?
You need that for the yellow center.
That's my point.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
I'll go with Pixel Cards 1, 4, and 7.
That is correct.
You will remain as the host.
Damn it.
PIXEL CARD 1: 90-DEGREE ROTATION,
PIXEL CARDS 4 AND 7: 180-DEGREE ROTATION
PERFECT MATCH TO THE TARGET
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu lost a life.
CURRENT STANDINGS
YONSEI: 0, KAIST: 2, POSTECH: 0
Samsung has a bright future ahead.
- What?
- Samsung.
Oh, because he majors
in semiconductor engineering?
THE FUTURE OF SEMICONDUCTORS IN KOREA
SEMICONDUCTOR SYSTEM ENGINEERING MAJOR
AND KAIST-SAMSUNG SCHOLARSHIP RECIPIENT
I'll go with Pixel Art.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
Please choose your opponent.
I'll play against
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu.
- Didn't he just beat Seung-gyu?
- Yeah.
That's cruel.
- Things might get physical after this.
- Looks like it.
If he keeps on hounding Team POSTECH only,
Team KAIST will make it back.
That seems to be their game plan.
Honestly speaking,
I saw Team Yonsei as a bigger threat.
I think we should target
a single team early on.
Why don't we strike Team POSTECH
when we have the host position?
Team POSTECH itself isn't our main target.
Team Yonsei
will probably target Team POSTECH,
so we should claim the points
before they can.
To keep Team Yonsei from winning points?
Exactly.
JEON JI-MIN CHOSE
TEAM KAIST CONTESTANTS 3 TIMES IN A ROW
Let's keep it cool.
The host, Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min,
chose Team KAIST's Jae Seung-gyu
as his opponent.
Team Yonsei will use the Priority card.
Seung-gyu is being replaced.
Team Yonsei must've thought
they had to cut in now for survival.
Team Yonsei's Choi A-in
used the Priority card.
My team expected to get overlooked
for two rounds.
That didn't mean
we had to just stand and watch.
The host will have a new opponent
for this round.
Team Yonsei's Choi A-in,
please come to the stage.
Good luck.
Let's have a good game.
I saw him beat two opponents back-to-back,
so I knew he wasn't going
to be an easy mark.
Still, I didn't let that make me nervous.
Is it 1, 4, and 7?
Aren't they the answer?
A-IN SOLVED THE PREVIOUS QUESTION
FASTER THAN JI-MIN
I want to volunteer.
I told myself, "He may be good,
but not overwhelmingly good."
I was actually expecting
that they would make a move
to take the host position.
A-in is a strong contender
with good results in the pre-test,
so I tensed up a bit.
Here is your question.
TARGET
Do they need yellow and red to get orange?
Yes.
They'll need Pixel Card 9.
I'll go with Pixel Cards 4, 7...
and 6.
Team KAIST's Jeon Ji-min.
That is incorrect.
PIXEL CARDS 4, 6, 7: WRONG COMBINATION
Come on, A-in.
Team Yonsei's Choi A-in.
I'll go with Pixel Cards 2, 4, and 9.
Team Yonsei's Choi A-in. That is correct.
I failed to win
as many points as I could as the host,
so that was disappointing.
- She took it from him.
- She did it.
- I got so nervous just now.
- Same here.
So Ji-min went down?
PIXEL CARD 2: 180-DEGREE ROTATION
PIXEL CARDS 4 AND 9: 90-DEGREE ROTATION
PERFECT MATCH TO THE TARGET
Team Yonsei's Choi A-in is the new host.
It was satisfying
to contribute to my team.
It gave me hope that I could lead
my team to victory and survival.
Such a shame.
CURRENT STANDINGS
YONSEI: 1, KAIST: 2, POSTECH: 0
Did I win two points?
I wasn't concerned before,
but I started to worry
that things might go down
after my initial loss.
How do we proceed?
I think we can wait it out.
She may choose one of us.
Team Yonsei's Choi A-in.
Please select the next game.
I'll go with Pixel Art.
Please choose your opponent.
I thought I had to choose someone
I could certainly defeat.
You think she's looking at me?
Maybe it's you.
Will she choose Team POSTECH, too?
- I won't blame them if they get offended.
- Me neither.
- She has to do what's best for her team.
- Yeah, that's true.
CHOI A-IN WALKS UP TO TEAM POSTECH
Do I have any volunteers?
When provoked, people tend to tense up.
I was hoping to intimidate them
with my surprise question.
I choose Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu
as my opponent.
- Okay, I'll see you later.
- Focus, okay? She's not so fast.
HOST: TEAM YONSEI, CHOI A-IN
OPPONENT: TEAM POSTECH, JAE SEUNG-GYU
That should make him mad.
WHY?
He got selected three times.
I was chosen three times in a row.
That didn't make me feel great, exactly.
It fueled my drive to win.
Here is your question.
TARGET
This one is difficult.
It's gotten much harder.
We had more empty cells in earlier rounds.
So soon?
Wow, he has a lot of fight left in him.
I'll go with Pixel Cards 4, 5, and 9.
PIXEL CARDS 4, 5, 9: WRONG COMBINATION
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu.
That is incorrect.
Your opponent will now get
the chance to answer.
Why is my heart racing?
You have five seconds left.
Come on.
Ten seconds have passed.
OPEN FLOOR AFTER 10 SECONDS
Both contestants are allowed to answer.
Please help us out, Seung-gyu.
I'll go with Pixel Cards 1, 5, and 9.
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu.
That is correct.
PIXEL CARD 1: 90-DEGREE ROTATION,
PIXEL CARDS 5 AND 9: 180-DEGREE ROTATION
PERFECT MATCH TO THE TARGET
That is correct.
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu
is the new host.
It felt amazing.
I finally got the chance
to show everyone my worth.
Team Yonsei used the Priority card,
but they only earned a single point.
They're in big trouble.
Team Yonsei's Choi A-in lost a life.
Please return to your place.
CURRENT STANDINGS
YONSEI: 1, KAIST: 2, POSTECH: 1
The host, Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu,
will now select the next game.
I'll go with Time Jump.
I'm so curious. I wanted to try that one.
All right. Time Jump!
I can't wait.
Good.
Please choose your opponent.
I wanted to get back on stage,
beat him, and reclaim the host role.
I wonder who he'll choose.
CHOOSE SOMEONE FROM TEAM KAIST
HAND SIGNAL RECEIVED
I'll play against Team KAIST's Kim Ji-u.
Team KAIST's Kim Ji-u,
please come to the stage.
Here's your question.
USE NUMBERS FROM 1 TO 6
(2-DIGIT) MINUTES PAST (1-DIGIT):(1-DIGIT)
IS (1-DIGIT):(1-DIGIT)
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu.
- Already?
- He has an answer already?
- So quick.
- He's so fast.
Please state your answer.
The answer is,
62 minutes past 4:01 is 5:03.
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu.
That is correct.
Is this the beginning
of a new king's reign?
I hope Team POSTECH crushes them.
- A shot at Team Yonsei...
- A shot at Team KAIST. Bang, bang.
CURRENT STANDINGS
YONSEI: 1, KAIST: 2, POSTECH: 2
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu.
Please select the next game.
I'll go with Time Jump.
Please choose your opponent.
Why don't you choose me?
Should I raise my hand?
Go with Team KAIST one more time.
Because we had seen
Team Yonsei playing an active role
in preparing strategies
for Mine and Trade,
we determined that
they would be harder to defeat.
That's why we decided
to target Team KAIST instead.
HOST: TEAM POSTECH, JAE SEUNG-GYU
I'll play against
Team KAIST's Kang Ji-hoo.
- This isn't good.
- Who did he want?
Someone from Team KAIST.
Let us begin Time Jump.
Here is your question.
USE NUMBERS FROM 1 TO 7
(2-DIGIT) MINUTES PAST (1-DIGIT):(1-DIGIT)
IS (1-DIGIT):(2-DIGIT)
That startled me.
Seventy...
My mind went blank after I blurted out 70.
I couldn't recall the answer.
Your opponent will now get
the chance to answer.
TEAM POSTECH CAN ANSWER NOW
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu.
The answer is,
76 minutes past 3:05 is 4:21.
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu.
That is correct.
He's good.
- He's really good.
- Seung-gyu is on fire.
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu
will remain as the host.
The new king's reign has begun.
Now, I don't even want Team POSTECH.
Why are they all so good?
I wish the winner didn't have to join us.
I hope the creators
will scrap the redemption round.
Seung-gyu has won
three consecutive rounds.
Team KAIST's Kang Ji-hoo.
You don't have any life left
and cannot compete anymore.
Please leave the main hall.
- Good luck, guys.
- We'll do our best.
It was very upsetting.
I felt terrible that I failed
to help secure our team's survival.
CURRENT STANDINGS
YONSEI: 1, KAIST: 2, POSTECH: 3
Please select the next game.
I'll go with Time Jump.
Who will he choose next?
He'll choose one of us now.
HOST: TEAM POSTECH, JAE SEUNG-GYU
I'll play against
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han.
Team KAIST again?
- He chose Jae-han.
- He's out to crush them one by one.
- Seung-gyu's good.
- I'm enjoying this.
Okay. You've got this, Jae-han.
Let us begin Time Jump.
Here is your question.
USE NUMBERS FROM 0 TO 7
They need a three-digit number?
(3-DIGIT) MINUTES PAST (1-DIGIT):(2-DIGIT)
IS (1-DIGIT):(1-DIGIT)
What?
Are you serious?
(3-DIGIT) MINUTES PAST (1-DIGIT):(2-DIGIT)
IS (1-DIGIT):(1-DIGIT)
NOTE: DON'T USE 0 FOR THE HOUR
Zero has to go in the middle
of the three-digit number.
It can't go anywhere else.
So the 3-digit number must be
in the 100s or the 200s.
I'd say it's in the 200s.
I thought,
"I'm so screwed. It's all over."
Please...
The answer is,
206 minutes past 4:35 is 7:01.
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu.
206 MINUTES PAST 4:35 IS 7:01
That is incorrect.
Your opponent will now get
the chance to answer.
You've got this, Jae-han. Take your shot.
You have five seconds left.
Ten seconds have passed.
Both contestants are allowed to answer.
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han.
The answer is,
205 minutes past 3:41 is 7:06.
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han. That is correct.
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han is the new host.
This changes everything.
That means Seung-gyu is out of life, no?
Team POSTECH's Jae Seung-gyu.
You don't have any life left
and cannot compete anymore.
Please leave the main hall.
REMAINING LIFE COUNT
TEAM POSTECH, JAE SEUNG-GYU: 0
CURRENT STANDINGS
YONSEI: 1, KAIST: 3, POSTECH: 3
The host, Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han,
will now select the next game.
I'll go with Time Jump.
Please choose your opponent.
Excuse me, Jae-han.
Why don't you choose one of us?
Come on, we're game.
I couldn't just stand there.
I had to do something.
So I threw down the gauntlet.
I'll play against...
I'll play against Park Seo-yeon.
Targeting one team
is the right strategy here.
- I knew he'd go with Team POSTECH.
- He had to.
He needs to be strategic.
Team Yonsei made a big blunder,
using the Priority card too soon.
They should've saved it.
I should've held on to the host position.
I'm sorry
I didn't get to keep it for long.
It's okay.
- Hello.
Here's your question.
USE NUMBERS FROM 0 TO 5
THE NEW QUESTION INVOLVES DATES
Finally.
We've got dates now?
(2-DIGIT) DAYS PAST (1-DIGIT)/(1-DIGIT)
IS (1-DIGIT)/(1-DIGIT)
NOTE: FEBRUARY ALWAYS HAS 28 DAYS
Where do we put the zero?
It can only go into the second digit
in the two-digit number, right?
Okay, then. That means
the first month is an odd month.
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han.
The answer is,
30 days past January 5th is February 4th.
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han. That is correct.
You will remain as the host.
TEAM POSTECH'S PARK SEO-YEON IS ELIMINATED
CURRENT STANDINGS
YONSEI: 1, KAIST: 4, POSTECH: 3
The host, Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han,
will now select the next game.
I'll go with Pixel Art.
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han
selected Pixel Art.
Please choose your opponent.
It's time to end Team POSTECH.
HOST: TEAM KAIST, KIM JAE-HAN
I'll play against Hwang Seok-hun.
Oh, man.
- Take your time.
- Okay.
- Don't worry about getting it wrong.
Wow, so smart.
We saw him flounder with Pixel Art.
Jae-han is amazing.
If Seok-hun wins this round
and Jun-u wins most of Photo Memory,
we have a good chance of survival.
Team POSTECH's Hwang Seok-hun,
please come to the stage.
Don't freeze up. Go get him.
I realized that I could wrap things up
if I could beat two POSTECH contestants.
That didn't seem like a huge challenge,
so I set my mind
on taking them down one by one.
- It's a rematch of their Deathmatch.
- That's true.
REUNION AFTER DOUBLE-SIDED BINGO
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han
got a bingo first.
KIM JAE-HAN DEFEATED HWANG SEOK-HUN
We need Seok-hun to win.
I hope Seok-hun will surprise all of us.
I wanted to secure a win no matter what.
Here is your question.
TARGET
Do your thing, Jae-han.
You were the best in this.
He beat all of us in practice runs.
Jeez, what a headache.
I'm completely lost this time.
It might be easier
to focus on primary colors.
It's the fastest to sort out the cards
based on the primary colors,
then the secondary colors on the sides.
That's a solid idea.
Team POSTECH's Hwang Seok-hun.
I'll go with Pixel Cards 3, 4, and 6.
Please be right.
He sounded so sure of his answer.
Team POSTECH's Hwang Seok-hun.
That is incorrect.
Your opponent will now get
the chance to answer.
That's a bummer.
This game is harder than it looks.
Plus, your mind goes blank
when you're out there.
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han.
I'll go with Pixel Cards 2, 4, and 6.
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han. That is correct.
PIXEL CARD 2: 180-DEGREE ROTATION
PIXEL CARD 4: 270-DEGREE ROTATION,
PIXEL CARD 6: 90-DEGREE ROTATION
PERFECT MATCH TO THE TARGET
I can't believe this.
- He's so good.
- He really is.
He's killing it.
- Jae-han won.
- He won again.
Team KAIST is likely to make it back.
We're so close, though.
If only we could beat Team KAIST...
- But we only have Jun-u now.
- That's true.
Team POSTECH's Hwang Seok-hun.
You don't have any life left
and cannot compete anymore.
Please leave the main hall.
Wow, he's an absolute genius.
How many games has he won now?
KIM JAE-HAN HAS WON 3 CONSECUTIVE GAMES
CURRENT STANDINGS
YONSEI: 1, KAIST: 5, POSTECH: 3
This round can be
Team POSTECH's last one, right?
Yeah.
But if Jun-u wins three rounds,
he can turn the tables.
Jun-u is the calm type, so--
- But if he loses, we're done.
- Well, I suppose.
Then, we're really out of the game.
TEAM POSTECH'S LAST SURVIVOR, LEE JUN-U
Please select the next game.
I'll go with Pixel Art.
Please choose your opponent.
Eliminate Jun-u, and we're done.
It's all over.
I'll play against Lee Jun-u.
Team POSTECH's Lee Jun-u,
please come to the stage.
I told myself if I took my time
and reviewed cards at my own pace,
then I'd be able to defeat Jae-han.
You can do this, Jae-han.
You're that good.
Please come through for us, Jun-u.
Let us begin Pixel Art.
Here is your question.
TARGET
This is super challenging.
Dang, it's making me dizzy.
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han.
Oh, what?
How is he pulling it off?
- He's so fast.
- Definitely.
I'll go with Pixel Cards 1, 3, and 9.
I can't bear to watch.
Oh, please...
Pretty please...
Team KAIST's Kim Jae-han. That is correct.
PIXEL CARD 1: 180-DEGREE ROTATION,
PIXEL CARDS 3 AND 9: 270-DEGREE ROTATION
PERFECT MATCH TO THE TARGET
Even if Team Yonsei managed
to defeat the remaining Team KAIST,
their total score
would only amount to four points.
As such, we will apply the mercy rule
and end the game.
- Oh, shoot.
- It's over.
How disappointing.
If only I had gotten
that Time Jump question right.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have chosen Jae-han.
Oh, Team KAIST's back in the game.
Damn it.
We went full savage
to get them eliminated, but...
Thank you for the good game.
- He beat four people all by himself.
- He's amazing.
How is this real?
KIM JAE-HAN ELIMINATED
ALL 4 CONTESTANTS OF TEAM POSTECH
That was a major boost to my confidence.
I thought I could contribute more
if I took on a more active role
in the upcoming games.
I'll take this
as a fresh shot at Elite League
and do my absolute best.
I felt disappointed in myself.
If only I had hit the buzzer
faster than Seung-gyu,
I could've stayed on as the host.
Looking back,
I realize I might have been too impatient.
I felt bad for my teammates, too.
Then again,
every good redemption round is brutal.
The winner gets a new shot.
We need some cruelty.
It was a fair game.
All teams were given the Priority card.
Team Yonsei should've saved it
so they could use it
when they knew they wouldn't lose.
- They used it too early.
- Right.
Now that it's come to this,
you could say Team KAIST proved
that they're better than these two.
Team KAIST went through two Deathmatches
and the redemption round.
They really made it back from hell.
That makes them more formidable
than Team KAIST of Season 2.
This was an opportunity
none of us expected.
We never imagined
that we could return to this hall again.
I wanted to try Photo Memory, though.
Same here.
It's a shame we never got to compete.
That concludes the redemption round,
Relay Match.
Now, the final results.
As Team KAIST obtained the most points,
Team KAIST won the match.
As the winner of the redemption round,
Team KAIST secured a second chance.
They can rejoin the surviving teams
and compete in Elite League Season 3.
Thank you.
Team Yonsei and Team POSTECH,
you failed to secure a second chance.
Please exit the grounds.
Good luck, guys.
Good job.
We're hard to get rid of.
We keep coming back.
We went through two Deathmatches
and barely managed
to win the redemption round.
Now that we're back,
we really should aim for the trophy.
Today's main match is Dilemma of the Mean.
What?
Dilemma?
- Sounds like a mind game.
- It's a mind game.
Let's make ourselves untouchable
and let the rest fight it out.
I do feel nervous.
Team KAIST made it back from hell twice.
Is it a revenge match?
Like, "We're back from the dead"?
We should've tried to get
in Team KAIST's good books.
There's no way
we can take Team KAIST down now.
We should smash Team SNU in Medicine.
We've got to be bold.
Hey, they're out to get us.
Everyone is targeting us.
This is a major make-or-break move.
What do we do now? We're in big trouble.
Yeah, really.
You could say Team SNU wasted their lives.
We're seeing the infighting of Team SNUs.
Let's not get involved.
- It's better for us.
- Team SNU is practically repaying us.
We must take a gamble to win.
Seriously though,
that's absolutely insane.
Subtitle translation by Jeongwoo Kim